
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "F#",
      "a#3",
      "d-",
      "c3"
    ],
    "answer": "d-",
    "music_key": "d-.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "g-#2",
      "g-",
      "c5",
      "f4"
    ],
    "answer": "c5",
    "music_key": "c5.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "A#1",
      "d4",
      "B2",
      "g#4"
    ],
    "answer": "d4",
    "music_key": "d4.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "g3",
      "A#",
      "F#",
      "c5"
    ],
    "answer": "F#",
    "music_key": "F#.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "a-2",
      "g-#2",
      "g-#",
      "G"
    ],
    "answer": "G",
    "music_key": "G.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "b-1",
      "c-#1",
      "g-#1",
      "f3"
    ],
    "answer": "g-#1",
    "music_key": "g-#1.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "a4",
      "e-2",
      "b-1",
      "g-1"
    ],
    "answer": "b-1",
    "music_key": "b-1.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "c#4",
      "a#3",
      "c-#2",
      "B1"
    ],
    "answer": "B1",
    "music_key": "B1.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "G",
      "f4",
      "g-",
      "C#"
    ],
    "answer": "g-",
    "music_key": "g-.mp3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key of this music?",
    "choices": [
      "e3",
      "d#3",
      "c4",
      "e-2"
    ],
    "answer": "d#3",
    "music_key": "d#3.mp3"
  }
]
